They're going nowhere... fast.
Superfast! is a comedy, action film directed by Jason Friedberg.
Undercover cop Lucas White joins Vin Serento's gang of illegal street racers.
They are fast and they are furious and they plan to double cross Los Angeles kingpin
Juan Carlos de la Sol, who hides his cash in a downtown Taco Bell.
Officer Lucas White, played by Alex Ashbaugh.
Vin Serento, played by Dale Pavinski.
Michelle, played by Andrea Navedo.
Jordana, played by Lili Mirojnick.
Detective Hanover, played by Gonzalo Menendez.
Sofia, played by Shakira Barrera.
(also known as Superfast & Superfurious and sometimes marketed as Superfast 8) is a 2015
American action comedy film written and directed by Jason Friedberg and Aaron Seltzer.
The film is a parody of the Fast & Furious film series.
It was released in theaters and VOD on April 3, 2015, to
coincide with the premiere of Furious 7.
The film explores themes of car race, parody, spoof.
The tone is lighthearted.